<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Despair on @dongthinhlong</title>
    <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/tags/despair/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Despair on @dongthinhlong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.6</generator>
    <language>vi</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dongthinhlong.github.io/tags/despair/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>14. God, I Have Doubts</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/14.-god-i-have-doubts/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/14.-god-i-have-doubts/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Someone from the crowd answered him, &amp;ldquo;Teacher, I brought you my son; he has a spirit that makes him unable to speak; and whenever it seizes him, it dashes him down; and he foams and grinds his teeth and becomes rigid; and I asked your disciples to cast it out, but they could not do so&amp;hellip;.It has often cast him into the fire and into the water, to destroy him; but if you are able to do anything, have pity on us and help us.&amp;rdquo; Jesus said to him, &amp;ldquo;If you are able! All things can be done for the one who believes.&amp;rdquo; Immediately the father of the child cried out, &amp;ldquo;I believe; help my unbelief!&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; -Mark 9:17-18, 22-24&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9. God, I&#39;m Afraid of Change</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/9.-god-im-afraid-of-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/9.-god-im-afraid-of-change/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For surely I know the plans I have for you, says the LORD, plans for your welfare and not for harm, to give you a future with hope. Then when you call upon me and come and pray to me, I will hear you. When you search for me, you will find me; if you seek me with all your heart, I will let you find me, says the LORD, and I will restore your fortunes and gather you from all the nations and all the places where I have driven you, says the LORD, and I will bring you back to the place from which I sent you into exile.&lt;/strong&gt; -Jeremiah 29:11-14&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
