<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Afraid on @dongthinhlong</title>
    <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/tags/afraid/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Afraid on @dongthinhlong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.6</generator>
    <language>vi</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dongthinhlong.github.io/tags/afraid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10. God, I Need to Confront Someone</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/10.-god-i-need-to-confront-someone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/10.-god-i-need-to-confront-someone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;god-i-need-to-confront-someone&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GOD, I NEED TO CONFRONT SOMEONE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not think that I have come to bring peace to the earth; I have not come to bring peace, but a sword. For I have come to set a man against his father, and a daughter against her mother, and a daughter-in-law against her mother-in-law; and one&amp;rsquo;s foes will be members of one&amp;rsquo;s own household.&lt;/strong&gt; -Matthew 10:34-36&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Christian, I am called to win over hearts and minds to Christ. But I am more often called to do so with gentle cajoling than with angry confrontation. There are two major problems with confrontation. First, if I am honest with myself, I will see that my confrontation is often rooted in my own anger rather than in Christian love. Second, in the promotion of Christian values and ideals, confrontation is often an ineffective tool. It causes the person being confronted to be defensive of the status quo rather than open to new ideas or new ways of life. If, however, I couch my words in unconditional love and acceptance, then that person will feel less threatened by the challenge to change. The old adage is true: I can catch more flies with honey than with vinegar.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9. God, I&#39;m Afraid of Change</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/9.-god-im-afraid-of-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/9.-god-im-afraid-of-change/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For surely I know the plans I have for you, says the LORD, plans for your welfare and not for harm, to give you a future with hope. Then when you call upon me and come and pray to me, I will hear you. When you search for me, you will find me; if you seek me with all your heart, I will let you find me, says the LORD, and I will restore your fortunes and gather you from all the nations and all the places where I have driven you, says the LORD, and I will bring you back to the place from which I sent you into exile.&lt;/strong&gt; -Jeremiah 29:11-14&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
