<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Worried on @dongthinhlong</title>
    <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/tags/worried/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Worried on @dongthinhlong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.6</generator>
    <language>vi</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dongthinhlong.github.io/tags/worried/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>13. God, I&#39;m in Despair</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/13.-god-im-in-despair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/13.-god-im-in-despair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When he reached the place, he said to them, &amp;ldquo;Pray that you may not come into the time of trial.&amp;rdquo; Then he withdrew from them about a stone&amp;rsquo;s throw, knelt down, and prayed, &amp;ldquo;Father, if you are willing, remove this cup from me; yet, not my will but yours be done.&amp;rdquo; Then an angel from heaven appeared to him and gave him strength. In his anguish he prayed more earnestly, and his sweat became like great drops of blood falling down on the ground.&lt;/strong&gt; -Luke 22:40-44&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>9. God, I&#39;m Afraid of Change</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/9.-god-im-afraid-of-change/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/9.-god-im-afraid-of-change/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For surely I know the plans I have for you, says the LORD, plans for your welfare and not for harm, to give you a future with hope. Then when you call upon me and come and pray to me, I will hear you. When you search for me, you will find me; if you seek me with all your heart, I will let you find me, says the LORD, and I will restore your fortunes and gather you from all the nations and all the places where I have driven you, says the LORD, and I will bring you back to the place from which I sent you into exile.&lt;/strong&gt; -Jeremiah 29:11-14&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2. God, I&#39;m Afraid</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/2.-god-im-afraid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/2.-god-im-afraid/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When it was evening on that day, the first day of the week, and the doors of the house where the disciples had met were locked for fear of the Jews, Jesus came and stood among them and said, &amp;ldquo;Peace be with you.&amp;rdquo; After he said this, he showed them his hands and his side. Then the disciples rejoiced when they saw the Lord. Jesus said to them again, &amp;ldquo;Peace be with you. As the Father has sent me, so I send you.&amp;rdquo; When he had said this, he breathed on them and said to them, &amp;ldquo;Receive the Holy Spirit&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; - John 20:19-22&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
