<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Change on @dongthinhlong</title>
    <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/tags/change/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Change on @dongthinhlong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.6</generator>
    <language>vi</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dongthinhlong.github.io/tags/change/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>16. God, Someone I Love Is Dying</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/16.-god-someone-i-love-is-dying/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 18 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/16.-god-someone-i-love-is-dying/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;As for me, I feel that the last drops of my life are being poured out for God. The time for my departure has arrived. The glorious fight that God gave me I have fought, the course that I was set I have finished, and I have kept the faith. The future for me holds the crown of righteousness which the Lord, the true judge, will give to me in that day.&lt;/strong&gt; -2 Timothy 4:6-8 (Modern English translation)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>13. God, I&#39;m in Despair</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/13.-god-im-in-despair/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/13.-god-im-in-despair/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When he reached the place, he said to them, &amp;ldquo;Pray that you may not come into the time of trial.&amp;rdquo; Then he withdrew from them about a stone&amp;rsquo;s throw, knelt down, and prayed, &amp;ldquo;Father, if you are willing, remove this cup from me; yet, not my will but yours be done.&amp;rdquo; Then an angel from heaven appeared to him and gave him strength. In his anguish he prayed more earnestly, and his sweat became like great drops of blood falling down on the ground.&lt;/strong&gt; -Luke 22:40-44&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>12. God, Please Help Me to Decide</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/12.-god-please-help-me-to-decide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 06 Sep 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/12.-god-please-help-me-to-decide/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For thus said the Lord GOD, the Holy One of Israel: In returning and rest you shall be saved; in quietness and in trust shall be your strength&amp;hellip;. He will surely be gracious to you at the sound of your cry; when he hears it, he will answer you. Though the Lord may give you the bread of adversity and the water of affliction, yet your Teacher will not hide himself any more, but your eyes shall see your Teacher. And when you turn to the right or when you turn to the left, your ears shall hear a word behind you, saying, &amp;ldquo;This is the way; walk in it.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt; -Isaiah 30:15, 19-21&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>10. God, I Need to Confront Someone</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/10.-god-i-need-to-confront-someone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/10.-god-i-need-to-confront-someone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not think that I have come to bring peace to the earth; I have not come to bring peace, but a sword. For I have come to set a man against his father, and a daughter against her mother, and a daughter-in-law against her mother-in-law; and one&amp;rsquo;s foes will be members of one&amp;rsquo;s own household.&lt;/strong&gt; -Matthew 10:34-36&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Christian, I am called to win over hearts and minds to Christ. But I am more often called to do so with gentle cajoling than with angry confrontation. There are two major problems with confrontation. First, if I am honest with myself, I will see that my confrontation is often rooted in my own anger rather than in Christian love. Second, in the promotion of Christian values and ideals, confrontation is often an ineffective tool. It causes the person being confronted to be defensive of the status quo rather than open to new ideas or new ways of life. If, however, I couch my words in unconditional love and acceptance, then that person will feel less threatened by the challenge to change. The old adage is true: I can catch more flies with honey than with vinegar.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
