<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Angry on @dongthinhlong</title>
    <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/tags/angry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Angry on @dongthinhlong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.6</generator>
    <language>vi</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dongthinhlong.github.io/tags/angry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10. God, I Need to Confront Someone</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/10.-god-i-need-to-confront-someone/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/10.-god-i-need-to-confront-someone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;god-i-need-to-confront-someone&#34;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;GOD, I NEED TO CONFRONT SOMEONE&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not think that I have come to bring peace to the earth; I have not come to bring peace, but a sword. For I have come to set a man against his father, and a daughter against her mother, and a daughter-in-law against her mother-in-law; and one&amp;rsquo;s foes will be members of one&amp;rsquo;s own household.&lt;/strong&gt; -Matthew 10:34-36&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Christian, I am called to win over hearts and minds to Christ. But I am more often called to do so with gentle cajoling than with angry confrontation. There are two major problems with confrontation. First, if I am honest with myself, I will see that my confrontation is often rooted in my own anger rather than in Christian love. Second, in the promotion of Christian values and ideals, confrontation is often an ineffective tool. It causes the person being confronted to be defensive of the status quo rather than open to new ideas or new ways of life. If, however, I couch my words in unconditional love and acceptance, then that person will feel less threatened by the challenge to change. The old adage is true: I can catch more flies with honey than with vinegar.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>6. God, I Blew Up Today</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/6.-god-i-blew-up-today/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 06 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/6.-god-i-blew-up-today/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Cain said to his brother Abel, &amp;ldquo;Let us go out to the field.&amp;rdquo; And when they were in the field, Cain rose up against his brother Abel, and killed him. Then the LORD said to Cain, &amp;ldquo;Where is your brother Abel?&amp;rdquo; He said, &amp;ldquo;I do not know; am I my brother&amp;rsquo;s keeper?&amp;rdquo; And the LORD said, &amp;ldquo;What have you done? Listen; your brother&amp;rsquo;s blood is crying out to me from the ground&amp;hellip;.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;em&gt;Genesis 4:8-10&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>4. God, I&#39;m Angry at You</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/4.-god-im-angry-at-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 04 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/4.-god-im-angry-at-you/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Those who passed by derided him, shaking their heads and saying, &amp;ldquo;Aha! You who would destroy the temple and build it in three days, save yourself, and come down from the cross!&amp;rdquo; In the same way the chief priests, along with the scribes, were also mocking him among themselves and saying, &amp;ldquo;He saved others; he cannot save himself. Let the Messiah, the King of Israel, come down from the cross now, so that we may see and believe.&amp;rdquo; Those who were crucified with him also taunted him.&lt;/strong&gt;
&lt;strong&gt;When it was noon, darkness came over the whole land until three in the afternoon. At three o&amp;rsquo;clock Jesus cried out with a loud voice, &amp;ldquo;Eloi, Eloi, lema sabachthani?&amp;rdquo; which means, &amp;ldquo;My God, my God, why have you forsaken me?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/strong&gt;
-Mark 15:29-34&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
