<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Up on @dongthinhlong</title>
    <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/tags/up/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Up on @dongthinhlong</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.147.6</generator>
    <language>vi</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://dongthinhlong.github.io/tags/up/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>10. God, I Need to Confront Someone</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/10.-god-i-need-to-confront-someone/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/10.-god-i-need-to-confront-someone/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Do not think that I have come to bring peace to the earth; I have not come to bring peace, but a sword. For I have come to set a man against his father, and a daughter against her mother, and a daughter-in-law against her mother-in-law; and one&amp;rsquo;s foes will be members of one&amp;rsquo;s own household.&lt;/strong&gt; -Matthew 10:34-36&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As a Christian, I am called to win over hearts and minds to Christ. But I am more often called to do so with gentle cajoling than with angry confrontation. There are two major problems with confrontation. First, if I am honest with myself, I will see that my confrontation is often rooted in my own anger rather than in Christian love. Second, in the promotion of Christian values and ideals, confrontation is often an ineffective tool. It causes the person being confronted to be defensive of the status quo rather than open to new ideas or new ways of life. If, however, I couch my words in unconditional love and acceptance, then that person will feel less threatened by the challenge to change. The old adage is true: I can catch more flies with honey than with vinegar.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>3. God, I&#39;m Angrytled</title>
      <link>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/3.-god-im-angrytled/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://dongthinhlong.github.io/posts/3.-god-im-angrytled/</guid>
      <description>&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;When the days drew near for him to be taken up, he set his face to go to Jerusalem. And he sent messengers ahead of him. On their way they entered a village of the Samaritans to make ready for him; but they did not receive him, because his face was set toward Jerusalem. When his disciples James and John saw it, they said, &amp;ldquo;Lord, do you want us to command fire to come down from heaven and consume them?&amp;rdquo; But he turned and rebuked them. Then they went on to another village.&lt;/strong&gt; (Luke 9:51-55)&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
